Hello friends, my name is Ashwani Kumar and
brother I work in II Bank, brother
I have been engaged in II Bank, that is, it has been
two months since I joined,
what is my experience and brother how
I have joined here in II Bank
and brother how can you join, brother if
you want to work in a private bank, then
also what steps you have to follow,
brother I am going to tell you here in today's video
and brother I will
tell you about how I got selected, how much is my salary, how I got selected
and it has been two
months since I got selected here and
what is my experience, I am going to
tell you here in today's video, so
brother if you are new to this channel, then brother first of all
you should subscribe to the channel,
brother definitely like this video,
now friends let's
start the video without wasting time here, first of all
friends I want to tell you that
if you
want to work in any private bank, then brother you should have
graduation mandatory
Friends, you should have 50
plus marks in graduation. Your
marks should be more than 50.
Now let's talk about
how I got selected. So
friends, what is there here in II Bank, that
brother, externally,
internally, there is no hiring here,
especially in IIC Bank, it keeps happening
in other banks. II Bank does
not hire anyone without experience.
If you have 1 year, 2
years, any number of years of experience in the banking sector, but
you should have a minimum of one year of experience.
After that,
friends, you are eligible to work in Aaa Bank.
Otherwise, if you do not have any
experience and brother, you do
not have any sourcing etc.
experience in the banking sector, then brother,
you cannot get a job in Aaa Bank. Yes, the
second option is that if you
do any course etc. of Aaa Bank here, then
you  You can directly get a good post
in a bank like a relationship
manager. There is a
PO course in ICICI Bank. In that,
you directly
get the post of a relationship manager in ICICI Bank,
which also gives you a good salary.
And brother, friends, there is another course for
deputy manager. There is a
deputy manager course in ICICI Bank. By doing that
too, you can get a job in ICICI Bank. Let's
talk about how I got
selected here. Brother, I have
one year of experience,
not in the banking sector, but I have a source due to which
I was able to get here. If
you also want to get selected, then brother, I will
tell you in the next video
how you can get selected here,
especially in ICICI Bank, ADFC, Axis,
Yamal Finance Bank, all the private banks,
there are hirings going on. If you want to
work in a private bank, then brother, I will
provide a link below.
If brother, you are not able to get an interview etc., then
brother,
prepare well for the interview
about the banking sector.  If you
want to learn about the banking sector, there's
a BFSI course.
You can do that.
I've also done a BFSI
course from PW. And
HDFC Bank is hiring regularly.
If you have a year
or two of banking experience,
you can get a job in any of them.
If you're a fresher, there are HDFC Bank, Axis Bank,
AU Small Finance Bank, and many
other banks that also
hire freshers. From there, you'll find the
first level, which is
for CASA, or for freshers,
in sales, or similar work.
If you're a fresher,
you
won't immediately find an office-based job
in the banking sector.
Talking about pressure, there's 100% pressure
in every bank, no matter which bank you
go to. You'll be under pressure, you'll have targets.
You'll have to manage sales for every bank,
even if you go into operations.  Whether you
go to the back end office or however you
go, if you go to the bank, then brother,
from 30 to 70, your sales are always 100 to
100% and whoever goes into sales,
brother, their 100 to 100% is sales, they have
no other work, so
brother, let me tell you my point, brother, I am also
in sales,
I am in the business credit card department, which are
business credit cards, I
sell them, we also have a target, we have to achieve the target
and brother, there is
pressure too, the rest also gets done fine, there is
no problem, if you work
then it will be fine, let's talk about the
salary, brother, brother, the salary is okay, right now I have a
package of 55 lakhs, which is my fixed amount
of ₹ lakh, the rest brother is okay,
if you are a fresher, you
want to work in II Bank or other private banks, then
brother, friends, you should give the interview,
I have given a link below,  whatsapp-web
AYM Finance Bank There are many banks, this goes on
in many banks brother. The
third question was how did I get
selected, so brother I will explain it properly
in a video, how
can you get selected, if you want to work in II Bank, then
brother how can you get selected, in that
I will also tell you
how I cracked its interview here and brother how I got
selected in it, friends I will tell you the complete details
in a new video, in that I can
also show you my offer letter, I
can also show you my salary slip, there is no
problem, otherwise brother if I
tell you about my experience, brother, you will get a
very good reputation for working in the banking sector,
you
also get a good salary, you
can also see growth, brother, if you
work in the banking sector, then brother you work in a job with a very
good reputation,
pressure etc. keeps on happening, it is
not a problem,
you are going to get pressure everywhere,
targets and sales, so  I am with you if
you want to work in the banking sector, then
if I talk about my experience,
brother, my experience is quite
good, it has been two months for me, till now there is no
problem, till now there is
no such thing that work is not getting done,
pressure is not being able to bear
or targets are not being completed, nothing like this has
come to me yet, it has been two months for me,
now it is going to be my third month,
my joining was on 3rd,
my joining was on 3rd January, which is going to be
two months now, two months means it will be
5th to 4 days, my two
months will be completed, rest brother,
I am selected in II Bank,
whatever further query you have, whatever question you have, whatever doubt you have, etc.,
you can write it here in the comment box,
whatever doubt you have, if you have any doubt,
if you want to give me any suggestion or
you want to ask any doubt  If you want, then
you must ask in the comment box,
I will cover it 100 to 100% in the next video
and brother, I will clear your doubts.
Friends, this is all for today, if you
also want to do a job in the banking sector, then
brother, a link is given below,
join it and brother, brother, subscribe to this channel
because brother, the upcoming
updates are going to be very helpful for you,
quickly subscribe to the channel
and like the video. See you in the
next and then take care bye.